Caleb Smith

An experienced web developer with extensive experience in customer service. Self-directed learner passionate about creating a variety of solutions to make life easier. Recently completed a full-stack coding bootcamp at ARCA focusing in Java, JavaScript and SQL.

Cabot, AR 72023 (**501)-554-0996**

c.smith997@hotmail.com

LinkedIn:

Caleb Smith LinkedIn
Github: Caleb Smith

EXPERIENCE

Arkansas Coding Academy, University of Central Arkansas, Full-Stack Software Development — Completed

June 2022 - December 2022

-A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in Java, SQL, Javascript, AngularJS, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS in order to build a full-stack web application.

North Hills Animal Hospital, Sherwood, Arkansas — Receptionist

November 2021 - PRESENT

- -Coordinating appointment times with clients.
- Pulling medical records for clients when needed.
- -Adhering to business policy when handling medications.

Walgreens, Sherwood, Arkansas — Customer Service Associate

October 2019 - November 2021

- -Customer Service and answering phones.
- -Working on and completing photo projects for customers in a timely manner.
- -Working with management to stock shelves, unload trucks, change signs and merchandising.

Wright, Lindsey and Jennings, Little Rock, Arkansas — Courier

September 2017 - August 2019

- -Mail retrieval and distribution to attorneys and secretaries.
- -Delivering documents to courts and businesses.
- -File retrieval from warehouse.

Languages

Java

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

SQL

AngularJS

Maven

Excel

Tomcat

Postman

RESTful Web Services

IDBC

Skills

Detail-Oriented

Programming

Adaptability

Organization

Time-Management

Critical Thinking

Problem Solving

AWARDS

Dean's List (4x) at University of Arkansas at Little Rock for maintaining a 3.5 GPA

Shoe Carnival, North Little Rock, Arkansas — Men's Department Lead

July 2016 - September 2017

- -Provide customer service, answer phones and handle cash
- -Supervise coworkers in my department to rotate stock get ready for incoming shipment.

EDUCATION

University of Arkansas at Little Rock, Little Rock, AR - Mass Communication (Motion Pictures)

August 2019 - December 2021

Graduated in December 2021 with a major in Mass Communication and a Minor in Internet Technologies.

University of Arkansas at Pulaski Tech, North Little Rock, AR, - Liberal Arts and Sciences

May 2018 - May 2019

Graduated with an associates degree in May 2019 in Liberal Arts and Sciences.

University of Central Arkansas, Conway, AR, - Accounting

August 2015 - April 2016

Started my college career majoring in accounting and also took my first Python course during this period which caused the switch in interests.

PROJECTS

The Studio Theatre — WordPress based with CSS https://www.studiotheatrelr.com/

As a team, worked with the client, The Studio Theatre, based in Little Rock, to build a web page for all consumers to use to learn about this non profit organization. On this site, you can buy tickets, learn about past productions, see what productions are coming up, learn about the casts and even donate!

Portfolio — HTML and CSS with JavaScript

https://csmitty97.github.io/portfolio/index.html

My personal portfolio that goes over all projects in both IT and filmmaking. This site itself is mainly HTML and CSS but the IT examples provided are JavaScript based.